<welcome>
    Alhamdulillah! Assalamu Alaikum!
    <br/>
    <br/>
    My name is <b>Al-Ahmadgaid Bahauddin Asaad</b>, I'm a data scientist at <a href="http://digenomix.com/">DiGenomiX Incorporated</a>, a tech-startup company developing health care solutions using <a href="http://www.scholarpedia.org/article/Deep_Learning">deep learning</a>. 
    I'm a statistician by training, with Master of Science in Statistics degree from University of the Philippines Diliman.
    My <a href="http://www.stat.upd.edu.ph/docs/graduates/grads_ms/1617/1617_ASAAD.pdf">research</a> was <i>Bayesian Autoregressive Distributed Lag</i> via <i>Stochastic Gradient Hamiltonian Monte Carlo</i>, advised by <a href="http://www.stat.upd.edu.ph/faculty.html#fmagadia">Dr. Magadia</a> (download the full copy <a href="pdf/new-thesis.pdf">here</a>). 
    At work, I'm involved on full stack development: from data cleaning, modeling to productization. Hence, I've also touched on software development both backend and frontend of the app (for desktop -- using <a href="https://www.wxpython.org/">wxPython GUI</a>; and web engine -- using <a href="https://electronjs.org/">electron</a> builder).
    I'm a heavy user of Python, R, Julia and Javascript (using frameworks such as <a href="https://d3js.org/">d3.js</a> for interactive visualization) programming languages with experience on C/C++ and Java.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    Lastly, I'm a fun of graphic arts and a great supporter of peace.
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <center>
        <div class="quote" align="center">
            <i>It is better for a leader to make a mistake in forgiving than to make a mistake in punishing.</i>
            <br/>
            <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad">Prophet Muhammad (S.A.W.)</a>
        </div>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <!-- <div class="quote" align="center">
            <i>Peace cannot be kept by force. It can only be achieved through understanding.</i>
            <br/>
            <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albert_Einstein">Albert Einstein</a>
        </div> -->
    </center>
    <!-- <br/>
    <br/>
    <br/>
    <br/> -->
</welcome>